A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1958-1970 FA400
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1962
  - Germany, 02.1962/717
    - Germany - Social Sciences, 02.1962/717.S
      - University of Munich (Sociology) (Reel 45, Frame 326)
  - Tanganyika, 02.1962/723
    - Tanganyika (Reel 45, Frame 332)
    - B-V (Reel 45, Frame 346)
    - Tanganyika - Medical Sciences, 02.1962/723.A
      - Medical Education (Reel 45, Frame 474)
  - Cameroon, 02.1962/735
    - 735 (Reel 45, Frame 478)
  - Togo, 02.1962/745
    - 745 (Reel 45, Frame 484)
    - Olympio, Sylvanus E. (Reel 45, Frame 531)
  - Greece, 02.1962/749
    - A-Z (Reel 45, Frame 535)
    - Greece - Medical Sciences, 02.1962/749.A
      - University of Athens (Reel 45, Frame 574)
  - Hungary, 02.1962/750
    - B-T (Reel 45, Frame 586)
    - Hungary - Nursing, 02.1962/750.C
      - Hungary - Nursing (Reel 45, Frame 604)
    - Hungary - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 02.1962/750.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 45, Frame 608)
  - Italy, 02.1962/751
    - A-Z (Reel 45, Frame 610)
    - Italy - Medical Sciences, 02.1962/751.A
      - University of Siena (Neurophysiology) (Reel 45, Frame 773)
    - Italy - Fellowships, 02.1962/751.E
      - Cali, Antonio (Reel 45, Frame 775)
  - Libya, 02.1962/758
    - University of Libya (Reel 45, Frame 777)
  - Liberia, 02.1962/759
    - University of Liberia (Weeks) (Reel 45, Frame 779)
  - Monaco, 02.1962/761
    Monaco
    - Oceanographic Museum (Reel 45, Frame 788)
  - Morocco, 02.1962/765
    - B-S (Reel 45, Frame 792)
  - Norway, 02.1962/767
    - B-U (Reel 45, Frame 817)
  - Iran, 02.1962/771
    - Iran (Reel 45, Frame 845)
    - A-U (Reel 45, Frame 847)
    - Iran - Medical Sciences, 02.1962/771.A
      - Pahlavi University (Medical School) (Reel 45, Frame 977)
    - Iran - Fellowships, 02.1962/771.E
      - Shafaie, Forough (Reel 45, Frame 981)
    - Iran - Declinations, 02.1962/771.F
      - Golzari, M. (Reel 45, Frame 988)
  - Portugal, 02.1962/773
    - A-Q (Reel 45, Frame 992)
    - Portugal - Nursing, 02.1962/773.C
      - School of Nursing (Reel 45, Frame 1031)
  - Angola, 02.1962/778
    - Angola Agricultural Research Institute (Macedo) (Reel 45, Frame 1036)
  - Rumania, 02.1962/783
    - Margineanu, Nicholas (Reel 45, Frame 1039)
    - Rumania - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 02.1962/783.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 45, Frame 1047)
  - Russia, 02.1962/785
    - K-U (Reel 45, Frame 1049)
    - Russia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 02.1962/785.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 45, Frame 1064)
  - Finland, 02.1962/787
    - Finland (Reel 45, Frame 1093)
    - F-W (Reel 45, Frame 1095)
    - Finland - Fellowships, 02.1962/787.E
      - Paakkanen, Jouko S. (Reel 46, Frame 1)
      - Paunio, J. J. (Reel 46, Frame 253)
  - Poland, 02.1962/789
    - Poland (Reel 46, Frame 273)
    - C-Z (Reel 46, Frame 276)
    - Poland - Nursing, 02.1962/789.C
      - Poland - Nursing (Reel 46, Frame 444)
      - P-U (Reel 46, Frame 494)
    - Poland - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 02.1962/789.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 46, Frame 501)
    - Poland - Fellowships, 02.1962/789.E
      - Poland - Fellowships (Reel 46, Frame 503)
      - A-Z (Reel 46, Frame 511)
  - Spain, 02.1962/795
    - A-S (Reel 46, Frame 637)
  - Sweden, 02.1962/800
    - B-W (Reel 46, Frame 674)
    - Sweden - Nursing, 02.1962/800.C
      - Sweden - Nursing (Reel 46, Frame 763)
  - Switzerland, 02.1962/803
    - B-V (Reel 46, Frame 765)
    - Switzerland - Medical Sciences, 02.1962/803.A
      - University of Basel (Medical School) (Reel 46, Frame 835)
    - Switzerland - Nursing, 02.1962/803.C
      - Le Bon Secours Nursing School (Reel 46, Frame 842)
    - Switzerland - Fellowships, 02.1962/803.E
      - E-H (Reel 46, Frame 880)
  - Near East Region, 02.1962/804
    - Near East Region - Fellowships, 02.1962/804.E
      - Near East Region - Fellowships (Reel 46, Frame 895)
  - Turkey, 02.1962/805
    - A-O (Reel 46, Frame 897)
    - R-Z (Reel 46, Frame 1025)
    - Turkey - Nursing, 02.1962/805.C
      - Istanbul University (Nursing) (Reel 46, Frame 1151)
    - Turkey - Fellowships, 02.1962/805.E
      - A-S (Reel 47, Frame 1)
  - Egypt, 02.1962/812
    - A-Y (Reel 47, Frame 97)
    - Egypt - Medical Sciences, 02.1962/812.A
      - Ain-Shams University (Medical School) (Reel 47, Frame 121)
    - Egypt - Nursing, 02.1962/812.C
      - Alexandria University (Nursing School) (Reel 47, Frame 131)
    - Egypt - Fellowships, 02.1962/812.E
      - Kholy, Abdo A. (Reel 47, Frame 150)
    - Egypt - Hookworm, 02.1962/812.H
      - Egypt - Hookworm (Reel 47, Frame 153)
  - Jordan, 02.1962/816
    - Dajani, Rafiq Wafa (Reel 47, Frame 155)
    - Jordan - Fellowships, 02.1962/816.E
      - Ayyash, Adil M. (Reel 47, Frame 160)
  - Syria, 02.1962/820
    Syria
    - B-S (Reel 47, Frame 175)
  - Israel, 02.1962/825
    - A-L (Reel 47, Frame 183)
    - Israel (Reel 47, Frame 180)
    - Israel - Medical Sciences, 02.1962/825.A
      - Hebrew University (Medical School) (Reel 47, Frame 227)
  - Lebanon, 02.1962/833
    - A-U (Reel 47, Frame 240)
    - Lebanon - Nursing, 02.1962/833.C
      - American University of Beirut (Reel 47, Frame 330)
  - Members and Meetings, 02.1962/903
    - Bingham, Barry (Reel 47, Frame 343)
    - Brace, Lloyd D. (Reel 47, Frame 370)
    - Bronk, Detlev W. (Reel 47, Frame 384)
    - Bunche, Ralph J. (Reel 47, Frame 394)
    - Coggeshall, Lowell T. (Reel 47, Frame 406)
    - Dickey, John S. (Reel 47, Frame 435)
    - Dryfoos, Orvil E. (Reel 47, Frame 446)
    - DuBridge, Lee A. (Reel 47, Frame 462)
    - Franks of Headington, Oliver Shewell, Baron (Reel 47, Frame 468)
    - Hardin, Clifford M. (Reel 47, Frame 491)
    - Hesburgh, Theodore M. (Reel 47, Frame 510)
    - Houghton, Arthur A., Jr. (Reel 47, Frame 539)
    - Kerr, Clark (Reel 47, Frame 560)
    - Kimberly, John R. (Reel 47, Frame 593)
    - Rockefeller, John D. 3rd (Reel 47, Frame 603)
    - Stanton, Frank (Reel 47, Frame 633)
    - Van Dusen, Henry P. (Reel 47, Frame 684)
    - Wood, W. Barry, Jr. (Reel 47, Frame 708)
    - Woods, George D. (Reel 47, Frame 731)
  - Publicity and Publications, 02.1962/912
    - Publicity (Reel 47, Frame 755)
  - Agriculture, 02.1962/923
    - Consultants (A-Y) (Reel 47, Frame 759)
- General Correspondence, 1963
  - International, 02.1963/100
    - Aitken, Thomas H. G. (Reel 1, Frame 1)
    - Allen, LeRoy R. (Reel 1, Frame 119)
    - Anderson, Charles R. (Reel 1, Frame 202)
    - Armstrong, Ray E. (Reel 1, Frame 373)
    - Baird, Guy B. (Reel 1, Frame 392)
    - Bell, Philip W. (Reel 1, Frame 474)
    - Black, Joseph E. (Reel 1, Frame 566)
    - Borlaug, Norman E. (Reel 1, Frame 668)
    - Bradfield, Richard (Reel 1, Frame 765)
    - Browning, J. Artie (Reel 1, Frame 878)
    - Buller, Roderic E. (Reel 1, Frame 927)
    - Burress, Charles G. (Reel 2, Frame 1)
    - Byrnes, Francis C. (Reel 2, Frame 68)
    - Carey, Donald E. (Reel 2, Frame 114)
    - Casals, Jordi (Reel 2, Frame 234)
    - Casorso, D. Roy (Reel 2, Frame 293)
    - Causey, Ottis R. (Reel 2, Frame 330)
    - Consultant (Christensen, Clyde) (Reel 2, Frame 412)
    - Consultant (Ingles, Thelma) (Reel 2, Frame 468)
    - Consultants (M-W) (Reel 2, Frame 597)
    - Council on Foreign Relations (B-M) (Reel 2, Frame 637)
    - Crawford, Robert W. (Reel 2, Frame 748)
    - Crowder, Loy V. (Reel 2, Frame 783)
    - Cummings, Ralph W. (Reel 2, Frame 832)
    - Davidson, Ralph K. (Reel 2, Frame 946)
    - Debevoise, Eli W. (Reel 2, Frame 1048)
    - de Rycke, Laurence (Reel 2, Frame 1081)
    - Dinning, James S. (Reel 3, Frame 1)
    - Diplomatic Services (A-Y) (Reel 3, Frame 80)
    - Downs, Wilbur G. (Reel 3, Frame 234)
    - Erion, Gerhardt W. (Reel 3, Frame 305)
    - Freeman, Wayne H. (Reel 3, Frame 333)
    - Gibler, John W. (Reel 3, Frame 368)
    - Gottdank, Mildred (Reel 3, Frame 433)
    - Grant, John B. (Reel 3, Frame 467)
    - Grant, Ulysses J. (Reel 3, Frame 492)
    - Greeley, Melvin G. (Reel 3, Frame 543)
    - Harrar, J. George (Reel 3, Frame 584)
    - Hayes, Guy S. (Reel 3, Frame 737)
    - Hunter, Thomas H. (Reel 3, Frame 817)
    - International (A-B) (Reel 3, Frame 869)
    - International (C) (Reel 3, Frame 1009)
    - International (E-U) (Reel 4, Frame 1)
    - Jennings, Peter R. (Reel 4, Frame 199)
    - Johnson, Harald N. (Reel 4, Frame 263)
    - Jonkers, Andries H. (Reel 4, Frame 330)
    - July, Robert W. (Reel 4, Frame 454)
    - Kerr, J. Austin (Reel 4, Frame 554)
    - Kokernot, Robert H. (Reel 4, Frame 713)
    - Krull, Charles F. (Reel 4, Frame 800)
    - Kuttler, Kenneth L. (Reel 4, Frame 840)
    - Leach, Arthur D. (Reel 4, Frame 909)
    - Loeb, Robert F. (Reel 4, Frame 945)
    - McKelvey, John J., Jr. (Reel 4, Frame 1014)
    - Mellor, John W. (Reel 5, Frame 1)
    - Morris, Milton E. (Reel 5, Frame 55)
    - Moseman, Albert H. (Reel 5, Frame 87)
    - Myren, Delbert T. (Reel 5, Frame 204)
    - Niederhauser, John S. (Reel 5, Frame 243)
    - Owens, Patrick N. (Reel 5, Frame 334)
    - Pino, John A. (Reel 5, Frame 403)
    - Rachie, Kenneth O. (Reel 5, Frame 467)
    - Richardson, Ralph W., Jr. (Reel 5, Frame 510)
    - Roberts, Lewis M. (Reel 5, Frame 548)
    - Ruttan, Vernon W. (Reel 5, Frame 578)
    - Slack, Samuel T. (Reel 5, Frame 742)
    - Shope, Robert E. (Reel 5, Frame 760)
    - Schultz, Theodore W. (Reel 5, Frame 818)
    - Sprague, Ernest W. (Reel 5, Frame 866)
    - Stakman, Elvin C. (Reel 5, Frame 973)
    - Stewart, Jane R. (Reel 5, Frame 1039)
    - Thurston, H. David (Reel 6, Frame 1)
    - Trapido, Harold (Reel 6, Frame 48)
    - Traywick, Jack Dee (Reel 6, Frame 237)
    - Trotter, Mildred (Reel 6, Frame 316)
    - United Nations (D-U) (Reel 6, Frame 361)
    - United Nations Educational Scientific and Cultural Organization (A-T) (Reel 6, Frame 566)
    - United Nations, Food and Agriculture Organization (Freedom from Hunger Campaign) (Reel 6, Frame 695)
    - United Nations, Food and Agriculture Organization (A-F) (Reel 6, Frame 745)
    - United Nations, Food and Agriculture Organization (G-W) (Reel 6, Frame 909)
    - United Nations, World Health Organization (Creelman, Lyle) (Reel 6, Frame 1034)
    - United Nations, World Health Organization (A-C) (Reel 7, Frame 1)
    - United Nations, World Health Organization (E-Z) (Reel 7, Frame 60)
    - Weaver, Warren (Reel 7, Frame 152)
    - Wellhausen, Edwin J. (Reel 7, Frame 191)
    - Wernimont, Kenneth (Reel 7, Frame 249)
    - West, Robert L. (Reel 7, Frame 280)
    - Williams, Roger W. (Reel 7, Frame 313)
    - Winegar, Elizabeth A. (Reel 7, Frame 354)
    - Worth, Charles Brooke (Reel 7, Frame 417)
    - Wortman, L. Sterling (Reel 7, Frame 498)
    - Wray, Joe D. (Reel 7, Frame 533)
    - Young, William R. (Reel 7, Frame 626)
    - A (Reel 7, Frame 677)
    - Ba-Bl (Reel 7, Frame 860)
    - Bo-Bu (Reel 7, Frame 951)
    - Ca (Reel 7, Frame 1051)
    - Ce-Ch (Reel 7, Frame 1113)
    - Cl-Cor (Reel 8, Frame 1)
    - Cou-Cr (Reel 8, Frame 196)
    - D-G (Reel 8, Frame 216)
    - H (Reel 8, Frame 436)
    - I (Reel 8, Frame 703)
    - J-L (Reel 8, Frame 819)
    - M (Reel 9, Frame 1)
    - O-P (Reel 9, Frame 253)
    - R (Reel 9, Frame 382)
    - S (Reel 9, Frame 507)
    - T (Reel 9, Frame 569)
    - W-Y (Reel 9, Frame 623)
    - International - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 02.1963/100.E
      - 100E (Reel 9, Frame 830)
    - International - Malaria, 02.1963/100.I
      - 100I (Reel 9, Frame 889)
    - International - Humanities and Arts, 02.1963/100.R
      - Urban Architecture (Reel 9, Frame 916)
    - International - Social Sciences, 02.1963/100.S
      - International Social Science Council (Reel 9, Frame 920)
    - International - Virus Studies, 02.1963/100.V
      - United Nations (World Health Organization) (Reel 9, Frame 922)
  - Applications for Employment, 02.1963/101
    - Leach, Richard P. (Reel 9, Frame 927)
  - United States, 02.1963/200
    - A-Ae (Reel 9, Frame 936)
    - Af (Reel 9, Frame 1067)
    - Ag (Reel 10, Frame 1)
    - Ah-Amb (Reel 10, Frame 127)
    - American Academy (A-P) (Reel 10, Frame 174)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science (C-T) (Reel 10, Frame 226)
    - American (A-B) (Reel 10, Frame 364)
    - American Council on Education (A-W) (Reel 10, Frame 415)
    - American (C) (Reel 10, Frame 560)
    - American (E-H) (Reel 10, Frame 725)
    - American (I) (Reel 10, Frame 844)
    - American (J-M) (Reel 10, Frame 1058)
    - American Nurses' Association (C-W) (Reel 11, Frame 1)
    - American Society of Agronomy (Denver Meeting) (Reel 11, Frame 158)
    - American (P-S) (Reel 11, Frame 382)
    - American (T-W) (Reel 11, Frame 608)
    - Am-Ar (Reel 11, Frame 646)
    - Association (A-R) (Reel 11, Frame 751)
    - As (Reel 11, Frame 926)
    - Atlantic Monthly (Reel 12, Frame 1)
    - At (Reel 12, Frame 121)
    - Au-Ay (Reel 12, Frame 163)
    - Ba (Reel 12, Frame 175)
    - Be (Reel 12, Frame 321)
    - Bi-Bo (Reel 12, Frame 448)
    - Bra-Bri (Reel 12, Frame 705)
    - Broa-Brod (Reel 12, Frame 747)
    - Brookings Institution (A-S) (Reel 12, Frame 766)
    - Broo (Reel 12, Frame 815)
    - Brown (Reel 12, Frame 854)
    - Brown University (A-W) (Reel 12, Frame 981)
    - Bru-Bu (Reel 12, Frame 1062)
    - Ca-Ce (Reel 13, Frame 1)
    - Ch-Ci (Reel 13, Frame 408)
    - Columbia University (A-W) (Reel 13, Frame 531)
    - Cl-Col (Reel 13, Frame 734)
    - Com-Cop (Reel 13, Frame 927)
    - Cornell Medical Center (A-S) (Reel 14, Frame 1)
    - Cornell University (A-W) (Reel 14, Frame 74)
    - Cor-Cot (Reel 14, Frame 428)
    - Council (A-S) (Reel 14, Frame 479)
    - Cou-Cur (Reel 14, Frame 942)
    - Da-De (Reel 14, Frame 985)
    - Di-Dr (Reel 15, Frame 1)
    - Du (Reel 15, Frame 171)
    - Ellis Island (Reel 15, Frame 315)
    - Ea-Es (Reel 15, Frame 502)
    - Fa (Reel 15, Frame 829)
    - Fe-Fm (Reel 15, Frame 908)
    - Ford Foundation (A-G) (Reel 15, Frame 1000)
    - Ford Foundation (H-I) (Reel 16, Frame 1)
    - Ford Foundation (L) (Reel 16, Frame 110)
    - Ford Foundation (M-W) (Reel 16, Frame 191)
    - Fo (Reel 16, Frame 248)
    - Fr-Fu (Reel 16, Frame 428)
    - Ga-Ge (Reel 16, Frame 543)
    - Gi-Go (Reel 16, Frame 673)
    - Group Health Insurance, Inc. (Reel 16, Frame 781)
    - Gr-Gu (Reel 16, Frame 954)
    - Harvard University (A-F) (Reel 17, Frame 1)
    - Harvard University (G-H) (Reel 17, Frame 196)
    - Harvard University (J-L) (Reel 17, Frame 470)
    - Harvard University (M-P) (Reel 17, Frame 571)
    - Harvard University (Q-R) (Reel 17, Frame 690)
    - Harvard University (S-W) (Reel 17, Frame 765)
    - Hac-Har (Reel 17, Frame 812)
    - Has-Hav (Reel 17, Frame 934)
    - Haw-He (Reel 17, Frame 1076)
    - Hi-Ho (Reel 18, Frame 1)
    - Hu-Hy (Reel 18, Frame 178)
    - Il-Inm (Reel 18, Frame 269)
    - Institute (A-H) (Reel 18, Frame 435)
    - Institute (I) (Reel 18, Frame 493)
    - Institute (J-S) (Reel 18, Frame 690)
    - Inter American - Inter University (Reel 18, Frame 782)
    - International (B-T) (Reel 18, Frame 810)
    - Io-It (Reel 18, Frame 933)
    - Ja-Je (Reel 19, Frame 1)
    - Johns Hopkins University (A-P) (Reel 19, Frame 120)
    - Johns Hopkins University, School of Advanced International Studies (F-W) (Reel 19, Frame 373)
    - Johns Hopkins University (School of Hygiene & Public Health) (Reel 19, Frame 477)
    - Johns Hopkins University (Sl-Tu) (Reel 19, Frame 574)
    - Jo-Ju (Reel 19, Frame 585)
    - Ka (Reel 19, Frame 840)
    - Ke (Reel 19, Frame 1042)
    - Ki-Ky (Reel 20, Frame 1)
    - La-Li (Reel 20, Frame 71)
    - Lo-Ly (Reel 20, Frame 288)
    - Ma (Reel 20, Frame 489)
    - Mc (Reel 20, Frame 786)
    - Me (Reel 20, Frame 825)
    - Mi (Reel 21, Frame 1)
    - Mod-Mon (Reel 21, Frame 218)
    - Moo-Mou (Reel 21, Frame 373)
    - Mu-My (Reel 21, Frame 540)
    - National (A-C) (Reel 21, Frame 587)
    - National Institute of Health (B-W) (Reel 21, Frame 900)
    - National (E-I) (Reel 22, Frame 1)
    - National (J-R) (Reel 22, Frame 191)
    - National (S-U) (Reel 22, Frame 312)
    - New York (A-T) (Reel 22, Frame 515)
    - New York (U-Z) (Reel 22, Frame 695)
    - Na-Ne (Reel 22, Frame 802)
    - Ni-Ny (Reel 23, Frame 1)
    - Oa-Oh (Reel 23, Frame 321)
    - Ok-Ox (Reel 23, Frame 550)
    - Pan American Health Organization, Medical Education (Information Center) (Reel 23, Frame 658)
    - Pan American (H-W) (Reel 23, Frame 950)
    - Pa-Ph (Reel 24, Frame 1)
    - Princeton University (B-W) (Reel 24, Frame 249)
    - Pi-Pri (Reel 24, Frame 365)
    - Pro-Pu (Reel 24, Frame 579)
    - Q (Reel 24, Frame 760)
    - Ra (Reel 24, Frame 783)
    - Re (Reel 24, Frame 845)
    - Ri-Roc (Reel 24, Frame 908)
    - Roe-Roy (Reel 25, Frame 1)
    - Ru (Reel 25, Frame 155)
    - Sa (Reel 25, Frame 262)
    - Sc-Se (Reel 25, Frame 438)
    - Sh-Sm (Reel 25, Frame 631)
    - Sn-Sp (Reel 25, Frame 798)
    - St (Reel 26, Frame 1)
    - Su-Sz (Reel 26, Frame 253)
    - Ta-Th (Reel 26, Frame 377)
    - Ti-Tw (Reel 26, Frame 670)
    - United States, Agency for International Development (A-W) (Reel 26, Frame 847)
    - United States, Agriculture (A-W) (Reel 27, Frame 1)
    - United States, Health Education and Welfare (C-T) (Reel 27, Frame 358)
    - United States (A-H) (Reel 27, Frame 446)
    - United States (I) (Reel 27, Frame 577)
    - United States (J-P) (Reel 27, Frame 773)
    - United States, State (A-Y) (Reel 28, Frame 1)
    - United States (S-T) (Reel 28, Frame 265)
    - University of California (A-B) (Reel 28, Frame 306)
    - University of California (C-G) (Reel 28, Frame 440)
    - University of California (H-M) (Reel 28, Frame 582)
    - University of California (N-R) (Reel 28, Frame 736)
    - University of California (S-Z) (Reel 28, Frame 813)
    - University of Chicago (A-B) (Reel 28, Frame 996)
    - University of Chicago (C-F) (Reel 28, Frame 1066)
    - University of Chicago (G-H) (Reel 29, Frame 1)
    - University of Chicago (Johnson, Walter) (Reel 29, Frame 120)
    - University of Chicago (M-W) (Reel 29, Frame 220)
    - University (A-C) (Reel 29, Frame 395)
    - University (D-H) (Reel 29, Frame 551)
    - University (I-L) (Reel 29, Frame 775)
    - University of Michigan (A-W) (Reel 29, Frame 885)
    - University (M) (Reel 30, Frame 1)
    - University (N-O) (Reel 30, Frame 323)
    - University of Pennsylvania (B-W) (Reel 30, Frame 543)
    - University of Pittsburgh (A-Y) (Reel 30, Frame 702)
    - University (R-S) (Reel 30, Frame 796)
    - University (T) (Reel 30, Frame 975)
    - University of Wisconsin (A-Z) (Reel 30, Frame 1119)
    - University (U-W) (Reel 31, Frame 1)
    - U (Reel 31, Frame 175)
    - V (Reel 31, Frame 263)
    - Wab-Wan (Reel 31, Frame 418)
    - War-Was (Reel 31, Frame 529)
    - Wat-Wax (Reel 31, Frame 655)
    - Web-Wer (Reel 31, Frame 701)
    - Wes (Reel 31, Frame 809)
    - Wh-Wi (Reel 31, Frame 928)
    - Wo-Wu (Reel 32, Frame 1)
    - X-Z (Reel 32, Frame 130)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 02.1963/200.A
      - B-C (Reel 32, Frame 483)
      - D-S (Reel 32, Frame 542)
      - Tulane University (Medical School) (Reel 32, Frame 623)
      - University (A-I) (Reel 32, Frame 815)
      - University (K-W) (Reel 32, Frame 898)
      - W-Y (Reel 32, Frame 1044)
    - United States - Nursing, 02.1963/200.C
      - B-Y (Reel 33, Frame 1)
    - United States - Natural Science and Agriculture, 02.1963/200.D
      - University of Notre Dame (Biology) (Reel 33, Frame 238)
      - A-V (Reel 33, Frame 417)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 02.1963/200.E
      - E-P (Reel 33, Frame 536)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 02.1963/200.R
      - A-S (Reel 33, Frame 541)
      - U-Y (Reel 33, Frame 831)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 02.1963/200.S
      - C-T (Reel 33, Frame 1014)
      - U-Y (Reel 34, Frame 1)
    - United States - Virus Studies, 02.1963/200.V
      - A-J (Reel 34, Frame 262)
  - California, 02.1963/205
    - 205 (Reel 34, Frame 410)
  - Guam, 02.1963/213
    - Torres, Luis A. (Reel 34, Frame 412)
  - New York, 02.1963/235
    - 235 (Reel 34, Frame 417)
  - Philippines, 02.1963/242
    - Administration (Reel 34, Frame 419)
    - A-C (Reel 34, Frame 439)
    - University of the Philippines (A-F) (Reel 34, Frame 473)
    - University of the Philippines (G-R) (Reel 34, Frame 597)
    - University of the Philippines (S-V) (Reel 34, Frame 719)
    - D-Z (Reel 34, Frame 876)
    - Philippines - Medical Sciences, 02.1963/242.A
      - U (Reel 34, Frame 961)
    - Philippines - Nursing, 02.1963/242.C
      - University of the Philippines (Nursing School) (Reel 34, Frame 975)
    - Philippines - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 02.1963/242.D
      - University of the Philippines (Agriculture Library) (Reel 34, Frame 1014)
    - Philippines - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 02.1963/242.E
      - 242E (Reel 34, Frame 1022)
      - B-V (Reel 34, Frame 1037)
    - Philippines - Humanities and Arts, 02.1963/242.R
      - University of the Philippines (L) (Reel 34, Frame 1069)
    - Philippines - Social Sciences, 02.1963/242.S
      - University of the Philippines (Reel 34, Frame 1120)
  - Puerto Rico, 02.1963/243
    - Puerto Rico Nuclear Center (January-May) (Reel 34, Frame 1123)
    - Puerto Rico Nuclear Center (July) (Reel 34, Frame 1147)
    - Puerto Rico Nuclear Center (October-December) (Reel 35, Frame 1)
    - B-U (Reel 35, Frame 44)
    - Puerto Rico - Medical Sciences, 02.1963/243.A
      - University of Puerto Rico (Medical School) (Reel 35, Frame 120)
    - Puerto Rico - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 02.1963/243.E
      - Fernandez-Lopez, Carlos (Reel 35, Frame 207)
  - Virgin Island (St. Croix, St. John, St. Thomas), 02.1963/257
    United States Virgin Islands
    - Esperian, John H. (Reel 35, Frame 209)
  - South America and Latin America, 02.1963/300
    - Administration (January-May) (Reel 35, Frame 214)
    - Administration (June-December) (Reel 35, Frame 380)
    - Inter-American Institute of Agricultural Sciences (A-S) (Reel 35, Frame 527)
    - Inter American Research Center - S (Reel 35, Frame 718)
    - B-I (Reel 35, Frame 811)
    - South America and Latin America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 02.1963/300.D
      - A-I (Reel 35, Frame 970)
  - Argentina, 02.1963/301
    - A-H (Reel 35, Frame 1054)
    - National Institute of Agricultural Technology (Agricultural Economics) (Reel 36, Frame 1)
    - I-W (Reel 36, Frame 137)
    - Argentina - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 02.1963/301.D
      - C-U (Reel 36, Frame 406)
    - Argentina - Fellowships, 02.1963/301.E
      - A-V (Reel 36, Frame 432)
  - Bolivia, 02.1963/303
    - F-U (Reel 36, Frame 495)
    - Bolivia - Medical Sciences, 02.1963/303.A
      - Medical Education (Reel 36, Frame 562)
    - Bolivia - Fellowships, 02.1963/303.E
      - 303E (Reel 36, Frame 657)
      - R-V (Reel 36, Frame 659)
  - Brazil, 02.1963/305
    - Brazil (Reel 36, Frame 666)
    - A-F (Reel 36, Frame 669)
    - G-R (Reel 36, Frame 787)
    - University (B-S) (Reel 36, Frame 991)
    - S-Y (Reel 37, Frame 1)
    - Brazil - Medical Sciences, 02.1963/305.A
      - University (B-S) (Reel 37, Frame 163)
    - Brazil - Nursing, 02.1963/305.C
      - R-U (Reel 37, Frame 205)
    - Brazil - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 02.1963/305.D
      - A-U (Reel 37, Frame 239)
    - Brazil - Fellowships, 02.1963/305.E
      - 305E (Reel 37, Frame 311)
      - A-S (Reel 37, Frame 317)
  - Chile, 1963/309
    - Chile (Reel 37, Frame 434)
    - Chile - Medical Sciences, 1963/309.A
      - University (C) (Reel 37, Frame 735)
    - Chile - Nursing, 1963/309.C
      - Chile (Reel 37, Frame 796)
    - Chile - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1963/309.D
      - A-U (Reel 37, Frame 799)
    - Chile - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1963/309.E
      - Chile (Reel 37, Frame 812)
      - B-S (Reel 37, Frame 819)
    - Chile - Declinations, 1963/309.F